Guide to the Charles J. Baldridge papers, 1889-1946.
Baldridge, Charles J. papers, 1889-1946.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Charles J. Baldridge papers, 1889-1946.
3463
Charles J. Baldridge
11.1 cubic ft.
Correspondence, bills, receipts, inventories, and record books.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Papers of Charles J. Baldridge, a farmer and beekeeper in Kendaia, Seneca County, New York. Correspondence, bills and receipts, 1889-1899, 1902-1946; daybook, 1890-1946; and farm inventories, 1902, 1903 of Charles J. Baldridge for honey and fruit production. Also, Treasurer's Book, Women's Mission Circle; Kendaia Baptist Church, Record Book, 1902-1910, 1936; Sunday School Superintendent Record Book, 1932-1940.
BIOGRAPHICAL NOTE
Charles J. Baldridge was a farmer and beekeeper in Kendaia, Seneca County, New York.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Correspondence, bills and receipts, 1889-1899, 1902-1946; daybook, 1890-1946; and farm inventories, 1902, 1903 of Charles J. Baldridge for honey and fruit production. Also, Treasurer's Book, Women's Mission Circle; Kendaia Baptist Church, Record Book, 1902-1910, 1936; Sunday School Superintendent Record Book, 1932-1940.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Baldridge, Charles J.; Kendaia Baptist Church (Kendaia, N.Y.); Women's Mission Circle (Kendaia, N.Y.)
Subjects:
Bee culture--New York (State)--Kendaia.; Agriculture--New York (State)--Seneca County.; Beekeepers.
Places:
Seneca County (N.Y.)--Religious life and customs.; Kendaia (N.Y.)--Religious life and customs.
Form and Genre Terms:
Accounts.; Daybooks.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
CONTAINER LIST
- Correspondence, 1889 (Box 1)
- Correspondence, 1890 (Box 1)
- Correspondence, 1891 (Box 1)
- Correspondence, 1892 (Box 1)
- Correspondence, 1893 (Box 1)
- Correspondence, 1894 (Box 1)
- Correspondence, 1895 (Box 1)
- Correspondence, 1896 (Box 1)
- Correspondence, 1897 (Box 1)
- Correspondence, 1898 (Box 1)
- Correspondence, 1899 (Box 1)
- Correspondence, not in alphabetical order, contains some personal letters, later years only business correspondence, 1889-1899 (Box 1)
- Correspondence, Oct. 1918-Apr. 1919 (Box 1)
- Correspondence, Apr.-Oct. 1919 (Box 1)
- Correspondence, Nov. 1919-July 1920 (Box 1)
- Correspondence, Aug.-Dec. 1920 (Box 2)
- Bills and receipts, 1920 (Box 2)
- Correspondence, 1921 (Box 2)
- Bills and receipts, 1921 (Box 2)
- Correspondence, 1922 (Box 2)
- Bills and receipts, 1922 (Box 2)
- Correspondence, 1923 (Box 3)
- Bills and receipts, 1923 (Box 3)
- Correspondence, 1924 (Box 3)
- Bills and receipts, 1924 (Box 3)
- Correspondence, 1925 (Box 3)
- Bills and receipts, 1925 (Box 3)
- Correspondence, 1926 (Box 4)
- Bills and receipts, 1926 (Box 4)
- Correspondence, 1927 (Box 4)
- Bills and receipts, 1927 (Box 4)
- Correspondence, not alphabetized, 1928 (Box 4)
- Correspondence, not alphabetized, 1929 (Box 4)
- Bills and receipts, 1929 (Box 5)
- Correspondence, 1930 (Box 5)
- Bills and receipts, 1930 (Box 5)
- Correspondence, 1931 (Box 5)
- Bills and receipts, 1931 (Box 5)
- Correspondence, 1932 (Box 5)
- Bills and receipts, 1932 (Box 6)
- Bills and receipts, 1933 (Box 6)
- Correspondence, 1934 (Box 6)
- Bills and receipts, 1934 (Box 6)
- Correspondence, 1935 (Box 6)
- Bills and receipts, 1935 (Box 6)
- Correspondence, not alphabetized, 1936 (Box 7)
- Correspondence, 1937 (Box 7)
- Bills and receipts, not alphabetized, 1937 (Box 7)
- Correspondence, not alphabetized, 1938 (Box 8)
- Bills and receipts, 1938 (Box 8)
- Correspondence, 1939 (Box 8)
- Bills and receipts, not alphabetized, 1939 (Box 8)
- Correspondence, 1940 (Box 8)
- Bills and receipts, 1940 (Box 9)
- Correspondence, 1941 (Box 9)
- Bills and receipts, 1941 (Box 9)
- Correspondence, not alphabetized, 1942 (Box 9)
- Bills and receipts, not alphabetized, 1942 (Box 9)
- Correspondence, 1943 (Box 10)
- Bills and receipts, 1943 (Box 10)
- Correspondence, 1944 (Box 10)
- Bills and receipts, 1944 (Box 10)
- Correspondence, 1945 (Box 10)
- Bills and receipts, 1945 (Box 10)
- Correspondence, 1946 (Box 11)
- Bills and receipts, 1946 (Box 11)
- Taxes, 1918-1933 and n.d. (Box 11)
- Treasurer's Book, Women's Mission Circle, Kendaia Baptist Church, 1902-1910, 1936 (Box 11)
- Sunday School Superintendence Record Book, 1932-1940 (Box 11)
- Financial Journal, Apr. 1890-Sept. 27, 1891 (Box 11)
- Financial Journal, Sept. 28, 1891-Apr. 1, 1893 (Box 11)
- Financial Journal, Apr. 3, 1893-Apr. 30, 1894 (Box 11)
- Financial Journal, May 1, 1894-Aug. 28, 1896 (Box 11)
- Financial Journal, Aug. 29, 1896-July 2, 1898 (Box 11)
- Financial Journal, July 3-Nov. 24, 1898 (Box 11)
- Financial Journal, Nov. 25, 1898-Aug. 31, 1901 (Box 11)
- Financial Journal, Sept. 1, 1901-Aug. 14, 1905 (Volume 10)
- Financial Journal, Apr. 1, 1908-Oct. 10, 1910 (Volume 11)
- Financial Journal, Oct. 10, 1914-May 26, 1916 (Volume 12)
- Financial Journal, May 27, 1916-Oct. 27, 1917 (Volume 13)
- Financial Journal, Oct. 29, 1917-July 29, 1919 (Volume 14)
- Financial Journal, Aug. 1, 1919-Aug. 19, 1921 (Volume 15)
- Financial Journal, Aug. 21, 1921-May 12, 1924 (Volume 16)
- Financial Journal, May 13, 1924-Nov. 22, 1926 (Volume 17)
- Financial Journal, Nov. 24, 1926-Aug. 24, 1928 (Volume 18)
- Financial Journal, Aug. 25, 1928-Aug. 31, 1928 (Volume 19)
- Financial Journal, Sept. 2, 1929-Sept. 30, 1931 (Volume 20)
- Financial Journal, Oct. 1, 1931-Sept. 15, 1933 (Volume 21)
- Financial Journal, Oct. 24, 1934-June 20, 1936 (Volume 22)
- Financial Journal, June 21, 1936-Sept. 24, 1937 (Volume 23)
- Financial Journal, Sept. 25, 1937-Apr. 30, 1939 (Volume 24)
- Financial Journal, May 1, 1939-Dec. 31, 1940 (Volume 25)
- Financial Journal, Jan. 1, 1941-Dec. 31, 1942 (Volume 26)
- Financial Journal, Jan. 1, 1943-Dec. 31, 1946 (Volume 27)
- Ledger book made up from entries in the Financial Journals listed above (Volume 28)
- Correspondence, 1902-1917 (Box 12)
- Farm inventories, 1902-1903 (Box 12)